CONTACT INFO

PHONE

+506 8721 9070

EMAIL

carlos_retana_@outlook.com

ADDRESS

Desamparados, San José, Costa Rica

SKILLS

- Web Development
- Teamwork
- Responsible
- Passion for Al

LANGUAGES

- Spanish native language
- English 60%

CARLOS RETANA VIQUEZ

PROFILE

I am currently studying systems engineering, I have also trained through courses where I have learned different methodologies. I have experience with CSS3, HTML5 and Javascript, I also have experience with libraries like React and Astro Build.

EDUCATION

Ingeniería en Sistemas de Computación

2020 - Present

Universidad Fidélitas

Desarrollo Web

Apr 2022 - Dec 2022

Alura Latam - ONE Oracle Next Education

Técnico en Diseño Gráfico

2015 - 2017

Tecnológico de Costa Rica

EXPERIENCE

ABC Design Diseñador Gráfico

2017 - 2019 Corporate identity and

logo design.

Vicar Médica Desarrollador Full Comercial Stack

2023 - Present Front-end and back-end

development.